<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>
<resources>    
    <string-array name="promissesarray">
   		<item>
    	    I Corinthians 16:9|For a great door and effectual is opened unto me, and there are many adversaries.
   	    </item>
		<item>
		    Psalm 23:1|The LORD is my shepherd; I shall not want.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    John 11:40|Jesus saith unto her, Said I not unto thee, that, if thou wouldest believe, thou shouldest see the glory of God?
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Philippians 4:19|But my God shall supply all your need according to his riches in glory by Christ Jesus.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Matthew 11:29-30|Take my yoke upon you, and learn of me; for I am meek and lowly in heart: and ye shall find rest unto your souls. For my yoke is easy, and my burden is light.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Philippians 4:6|Be careful for nothing; but in every thing by prayer and supplication with thanksgiving let your requests be made known unto God.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Psalm 6:9|The LORD hath heard my supplication; the LORD will receive my prayer.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    I Corinthians 8:3|But if any man love God, the same is known of him.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Psalm 118:6|The LORD is on my side; I will not fear: what can man do unto me?
	    </item>
		<item>
		    I Thessalonians 5:17|Pray without ceasing.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    James 1:3|Knowing this, that the trying of your faith worketh patience.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Psalm 3:5|I laid me down and slept; I awaked; for the LORD sustained me.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Mark 16:15|And he said unto them, Go ye into all the world, and preach the gospel to every creature.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Psalm 30:5|For his anger endureth but a moment; in his favour is life: weeping may endure for a night, but joy cometh in the morning.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Revelation 21:4|And God shall wipe away all tears from their eyes; and there shall be no more death, neither sorrow, nor crying, neither shall there be any more pain: for the former things are passed away.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Revelation 3:11|Behold, I come quickly: hold that fast which thou hast, that no man take thy crown.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Malachi 3:1|Behold, I will send my messenger, and he shall prepare the way before me: and the LORD, whom ye seek, shall suddenly come to his temple, even the messenger of the covenant, whom ye delight in: behold, he shall come, saith the LORD of hosts.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    I John 2:23|Whosoever denieth the Son, the same hath not the Father: he that acknowledgeth the Son hath the Father also.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Psalm 60:12|Through God we shall do valiantly: for he it is that shall tread down our enemies.
	    </item>
		<item>
		    Jeremiah 15:19|Therefore thus saith the LORD, If thou return, then will I bring thee again, and thou shalt stand before me: and if thou take forth the precious from the vile, thou shalt be as my mouth: let them return unto thee; but return not thou unto them.
	    </item>
		<item>Acts 14:22|... we must through much tribulation enter into the kingdom of God.</item>
		<item>Psalm 121:2|My help cometh from the LORD, which made heaven and earth.</item>
		<item>Acts 20:35|I have shewed you all things, how that so labouring ye ought to support the weak, and to remember the words of the Lord Jesus, how he said, It is more blessed to give than to receive.</item>
		<item>John 15:15|Henceforth I call you not servants; for the servant knoweth not what his lord doeth: but I have called you friends; for all things that I have heard of my Father I have made known unto you.</item>
		<item>Psalm 119:137|Righteous art thou, O LORD, and upright are thy judgments.</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 10:14|Wherefore, my dearly beloved, flee from idolatry.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 43:18|Remember ye not the former things, neither consider the things of old.</item>
		<item>Matthew 11:6|And blessed is he, whosoever shall not be offended in me.</item>
		<item>Acts 3:19|Repent ye therefore, and be converted, that your sins may be blotted out, when the times of refreshing shall come from the presence of the Lord.</item>
		<item>Deuteronomy 4:31|(For the LORD thy God is a merciful God;) he will not forsake thee, neither destroy thee, nor forget the covenant of thy fathers which he sware unto them.</item>
		<item>Psalm 62:1|Truly my soul waiteth upon God: from him cometh my salvation.</item>
		<item>John 15:9|As the Father hath loved me, so have I loved you: continue ye in my love.</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 5:13|But them that are without God judgeth. Therefore put away from among yourselves that wicked person.</item>
		<item>II Corinthians 3:12|Seeing then that we have such hope, we use great plainness of speech.</item>
		<item>Exodus 20:16|Thou shalt not bear false witness against thy neighbour.</item>
		<item>Philippians 4:5|Let your moderation be known unto all men. The Lord is at hand.</item>
		<item>Job 6:24|Teach me, and I will hold my tongue: and cause me to understand wherein I have erred.</item>
		<item>Exodus 14:14|The LORD shall fight for you, and ye shall hold your peace.</item>
		<item>I Timothy 2:1,3|I exhort therefore, that, first of all, supplications, prayers, intercessions, and giving of thanks, be made for all men;...For this is good and acceptable in the sight of God our Saviour.</item>
		<item>Job 5:19|He shall deliver thee in six troubles: yea, in seven there shall no evil touch thee.</item>
		<item>I Thessalonians 5:18|In every thing give thanks: for this is the will of God in Christ Jesus concerning you.</item>
		<item>Philippians 1:29|For unto you it is given in the behalf of Christ, not only to believe on him, but also to suffer for his sake.</item>
		<item>Psalm 40:17|But I am poor and needy; yet the Lord thinketh upon me: thou art my help and my deliverer; make no tarrying, O my God.</item>
		<item>Mark 4:40|And he said unto them, Why are ye so fearful? how is it that ye have no faith?</item>
		<item>Job 5:2|For wrath killeth the foolish man, and envy slayeth the silly one.</item>
		<item>John 16:33|These things I have spoken unto you, that in me ye might have peace. In the world ye shall have tribulation: but be of good cheer; I have overcome the world.</item>
		<item>John 8:36|If the Son therefore shall make you free, ye shall be free indeed.</item>
		<item>Philippians 4:4|Rejoice in the Lord always: and again I say, Rejoice.</item>
		<item>Psalm 68:19|Blessed be the Lord, who daily loadeth us with benefits, even the God of our salvation. Selah.</item>
		<item>I Thessalonians 5:22|Abstain from all appearance of evil.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 28:26|For his God doth instruct him to discretion, and doth teach him.</item>
		<item>Matthew 20:27|And whosoever will be chief among you, let him be your servant:</item>
		<item>Philippians 1:29|For unto you it is given in the behalf of Christ, not only to believe on him, but also to suffer for his sake.</item>
		<item>Epheasians 6:11|Put on the whole armour of God, that ye may be able to stand against the wiles of the devil.</item>
		<item>James 1:20|For the wrath of man worketh not the righteousness of God.</item>
		<item>Hebrews 11:1|Now faith is the substance of things hoped for, the evidence of things not seen.</item>
		<item>Hebrews 12:6|For whom the Lord loveth he chasteneth, and scourgeth every son whom he receiveth.</item>
		<item>Epheasians 6:2-3|Honour thy father and mother; which is the first commandment with promise;That it may be well with thee, and thou mayest live long on the earth.</item>
		<item>Job 35:12|There they cry, but none giveth answer, because of the pride of evil men.</item>
		<item>Psalm 48:14|For this God is our God for ever and ever: he will be our guide even unto death.</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 14:40|Let all things be done decently and in order.</item>
		<item>Job 8:21|Till he fill thy mouth with laughing, and thy lips with rejoicing.</item>
		<item>Hebrews 13:5|Let your conversation be without covetousness; and be content with such things as ye have: for he hath said, I will never leave thee, nor forsake thee.</item>
		<item>I Peter 5:7|Casting all your care upon him; for he careth for you.</item>
		<item>Hebrews 13:6|So that we may boldly say, The Lord is my helper, and I will not fear what man shall do unto me.</item>
		<item>Hebrews 13:8|Jesus Christ the same yesterday, and to day, and for ever.</item>
		<item>Psalm 27:1|The LORD is my light and my salvation; whom shall I fear? the LORD is the strength of my life; of whom shall I be afraid?</item>
		<item>Psalm 64:10|The righteous shall be glad in the LORD, and shall trust in him; and all the upright in heart shall glory.</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 13:7|Beareth all things, believeth all things, hopeth all things, endureth all things.</item>
		<item>I Thessalonians 5:24|Faithful is he that calleth you, who also will do it.</item>
		<item>I John 1:9|If we confess our sins, he is faithful and just to forgive us our sins, and to cleanse us from all unrighteousness.</item>
		<item>Psalm 91:15|He shall call upon me, and I will answer him: I will be with him in trouble; I will deliver him, and honour him.</item>
		<item>Revelation 2:25|But that which ye have already hold fast till I come.</item>
		<item>Psalm 57:2|I will cry unto God most high; unto God that performeth all things for me.</item>
		<item>I John 3:21|Beloved, if our heart condemn us not, then have we confidence toward God.</item>
		<item>I John 5:2|By this we know that we love the children of God, when we love God, and keep his commandments.</item>
		<item>Exodus 20:3|Thou shalt have no other gods before me.</item>
		<item>Acts 8:22|Repent therefore of this thy wickedness, and pray God, if perhaps the thought of thine heart may be forgiven thee.</item>
		<item>Mark 13:31|Heaven and earth shall pass away: but my words shall not pass away.</item>
		<item>Psalm 31:24|Be of good courage, and he shall strengthen your heart, all ye that hope in the LORD.</item>
		<item>James 4:10|Humble yourselves in the sight of the Lord, and he shall lift you up.</item>
		<item>Job 36:11|If they obey and serve him, they shall spend their days in prosperity, and their years in pleasures.</item>
		<item>I Thessalonians 5:9|For God hath not appointed us to wrath, but to obtain salvation by our Lord Jesus Christ.</item>
		<item>Matthew 22:14|For many are called, but few are chosen.</item>
		<item>John 14:14|If ye shall ask any thing in my name, I will do it.</item>
		<item>II Corinthians 12:10|Therefore I take pleasure in infirmities, in reproaches, in necessities, in persecutions, in distresses for Christ\'s sake: for when I am weak, then am I strong.</item>
		<item>Hosea 13:5|I did know thee in the wilderness, in the land of great drought.</item>
		<item>II Peter 3:9|The Lord is not slack concerning his promise, as some men count slackness; but is longsuffering to us-ward, not willing that any should perish, but that all should come to repentance.</item>
		<item>Hebrews 4:12|For the word of God is quick, and powerful, and sharper than any twoedged sword, piercing even to the dividing asunder of soul and spirit, and of the joints and marrow, and is a discerner of the thoughts and intents of the heart.</item>
		<item>II Samuel 22:33|God is my strength and power: and he maketh my way perfect.</item>
		<item>II Timothy 1:7|For God hath not given us the spirit of fear; but of power, and of love, and of a sound mind.</item>
		<item>Nahum 2:1|He that dasheth in pieces is come up before thy face: keep the munition, watch the way, make thy loins strong, fortify thy power mightily.</item>
		<item>Matthew 10:38|And he that taketh not his cross, and followeth after me, is not worthy of me.</item>
		<item>Job 35:4|I will answer thee, and thy companions with thee.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 41:10|Fear thou not; for I am with thee: be not dismayed; for I am thy God: I will strengthen thee; yea, I will help thee; yea, I will uphold thee with the right hand of my righteousness.</item>
		<item>Matthew 15:16|And Jesus said, Are ye also yet without understanding?</item>
		<item>Isaiah 43:11|I, even I, am the LORD; and beside me there is no saviour.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 43:13|Yea, before the day was I am he; and there is none that can deliver out of my hand: I will work, and who shall let it?</item>
		<item>Revelation 14:7|Saying with a loud voice, Fear God, and give glory to him; for the hour of his judgment is come: and worship him that made heaven, and earth, and the sea, and the fountains of waters.</item>
		<item>Nahum 1:3|The LORD is slow to anger, and great in power, and will not at all acquit the wicked: the LORD hath his way in the whirlwind and in the storm, and the clouds are the dust of his feet.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 32:18|And my people shall dwell in a peaceable habitation, and in sure dwellings, and in quiet resting places.</item>
		<item>Matthew 6:14|For if ye forgive men their trespasses, your heavenly Father will also forgive you:</item>
		<item>Psalm 101:7|He that worketh deceit shall not dwell within my house: he that telleth lies shall not tarry in my sight.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 15:13|A merry heart maketh a cheerful countenance: but by sorrow of the heart the spirit is broken.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 43:2|When thou passest through the waters, I will be with thee; and through the rivers, they shall not overflow thee: when thou walkest through the fire, thou shalt not be burned; neither shall the flame kindle upon thee.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 49:16|Behold, I have graven thee upon the palms of my hands; thy walls are continually before me.</item>
		<item>Psalm 101:6|Mine eyes shall be upon the faithful of the land, that they may dwell with me: he that walketh in a perfect way, he shall serve me.</item>
		<item>Matthew 5:8|Blessed are the pure in heart: for they shall see God.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 51:12|I, even I, am he that comforteth you: who art thou, that thou shouldest be afraid of a man that shall die, and of the son of man which shall be made as grass.</item>
		<item>Psalm 50:15|And call upon me in the day of trouble: I will deliver thee, and thou shalt glorify me.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 2:6|For the LORD giveth wisdom: out of his mouth cometh knowledge and understanding.</item>
		<item>Psalm 37:22|For such as be blessed of him shall inherit the earth; and they that be cursed of him shall be cut off.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 23:26|My son, give me thine heart, and let thine eyes observe my ways.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 55:6|Seek ye the LORD while he may be found, call ye upon him while he is near.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 55:8|For my thoughts are not your thoughts, neither are your ways my ways, saith the LORD.</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 17:14|Heal me, O LORD, and I shall be healed; save me, and I shall be saved: for thou art my praise.</item>
		<item>John 14:18|I will not leave you comfortless: I will come to you.</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 17:7|Blessed is the man that trusteth in the LORD, and whose hope the LORD is.</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 21:8|And unto this people thou shalt say, Thus saith the LORD; Behold, I set before you the way of life, and the way of death.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 59:1|Behold, the LORD\'s hand is not shortened, that it cannot save; neither his ear heavy, that it cannot hear</item>
		<item>Job 11:10|If he cut off, and shut up, or gather together, then who can hinder him?</item>
		<item>Luke 24:49|And, behold, I send the promise of my Father upon you: but tarry ye in the city of Jerusalem, until ye be endued with power from on high.</item>
		<item>II Kings 11:5|And he commanded them, saying, This is the thing that ye shall do</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 29:12–13|Then shall ye call upon me, and ye shall go and pray unto me, and I will hearken unto you. And ye shall seek me, and find me, when ye shall search for me with all your heart.</item>
		<item>Psalm 36:12|There are the workers of iniquity fallen: they are cast down, and shall not be able to rise.</item>
		<item>Psalm 33:12|Blessed is the nation whose God is the LORD; and the people whom he hath chosen for his own inheritance.</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 29:13|And ye shall seek me, and find me, when ye shall search for me with all your heart.</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 33:3|Call unto me, and I will answer thee, and show thee great and mighty things, which thou knowest not.</item>
		<item>Psalm 112:5|A good man sheweth favour, and lendeth: he will guide his affairs with discretion.</item>
		<item>Job 19:25|For I know that my redeemer liveth, and that he shall stand at the latter day upon the earth.</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 10:12|Wherefore let him that thinketh he standeth take heed lest he fall.</item>
		<item>Matthew 24:13|But he that shall endure unto the end, the same shall be saved.</item>
		<item>Job 33:4|The spirit of God hath made me, and the breath of the Almighty hath given me life.</item>
		<item>Psalm 119:11|Thy word have I hid in mine heart, that I might not sin against thee.</item>
		<item>I John 4:10|Herein is love, not that we loved God, but that he loved us, and sent his Son to be the propitiation for our sins.</item>
		<item>James 5:8|Be ye also patient; stablish your hearts: for the coming of the Lord draweth nigh.</item>
		<item>I John 4:8|He that loveth not knoweth not God; for God is love.</item>
		<item>Luke 5:32|I came not to call the righteous, but sinners to repentance.</item>
		<item>John 10:10|The thief cometh not, but for to steal, and to kill, and to destroy: I am come that they might have life, and that they might have it more abundantly.</item>
		<item>John 11:25|Jesus said unto her, I am the resurrection, and the life: he that believeth in me, though he were dead, yet shall he live:</item>
		<item>John 13:7|Jesus answered and said unto him, What I do thou knowest not now; but thou shalt know hereafter.</item>
		<item>Psalm 51:17|The sacrifices of God are a broken spirit: a broken and a contrite heart, O God, thou wilt not despise.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 24:10|If thou faint in the day of adversity, thy strength is small.</item>
		<item>John 14:13|And whatsoever ye shall ask in my name, that will I do, that the Father may be glorified in the Son.</item>
		<item>John 4:24|God is a Spirit: and they that worship him must worship him in spirit and in truth.</item>
		<item>Epheasians 6:10|Finally, my brethren, be strong in the Lord, and in the power of his might.</item>
		<item>John 10:10|The thief cometh not, but for to steal, and to kill, and to destroy: I am come that they might have life, and that they might have it more abundantly.</item>
		<item>John 10:11|I am the good shepherd: the good shepherd giveth his life for the sheep.</item>
		<item>John 10:9|I am the door: by me if any man enter in, he shall be saved, and shall go in and out, and find pasture.</item>
		<item>Numbers 6:24–26|The LORD bless thee, and keep thee:The LORD make his face shine upon thee, and be gracious unto thee:The LORD lift up his countenance upon thee, and give thee peace.</item>
		<item>Job 8:20|Behold, God will not cast away a perfect man, neither will he help the evil doers.</item>
		<item>Deuteronomy 11:26|Behold, I set before you this day a blessing and a curse</item>
		<item>II Corinthians 12:9|And he said unto me, My grace is sufficient for thee: for my strength is made perfect in weakness. Most gladly therefore will I rather glory in my infirmities, that the power of Christ may rest upon me.</item>
		<item>John 7:24|Judge not according to the appearance, but judge righteous judgment.</item>
		<item>John 17:15|I pray not that thou shouldest take them out of the world, but that thou shouldest keep them from the evil.</item>
		<item>John 8:12|Then spake Jesus again unto them, saying, I am the light of the world: he that followeth me shall not walk in darkness, but shall have the light of life.</item>
		<item>Psalm 97:7|Confounded be all they that serve graven images, that boast themselves of idols: worship him, all ye gods.</item>
		<item>Psalm 2:11|Serve the LORD with fear, and rejoice with trembling.</item>
		<item>John 5:41|I receive not honour from men.</item>
		<item>John 15:17|These things I command you, that ye love one another.</item>
		<item>II Timothy 2:1|Thou therefore, my son, be strong in the grace that is in Christ Jesus.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 35:3|Strengthen ye the weak hands, and confirm the feeble knees.</item>
		<item>Hosea 13:14|I will ransom them from the power of the grave; I will redeem them from death: O death, I will be thy plagues; O grave, I will be thy destruction: repentance shall be hid from mine eyes.</item>
		<item>Galatians 3:26|For ye are all the children of God by faith in Christ Jesus.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 43:15|I am the LORD, your Holy One, the creator of Israel, your King.</item>
		<item>John 8:32|And ye shall know the truth, and the truth shall make you free.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 22:8|He that soweth iniquity shall reap vanity: and the rod of his anger shall fail.</item>
		<item>Joshua 1:5|… I will not fail thee, nor forsake thee.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 3:12|For whom the LORD loveth he correcteth; even as a father the son in whom he delighteth.</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 7:8|Behold, ye trust in lying words, that cannot profit.</item>
		<item>Lamentations 3:26|It is good that a man should both hope and quietly wait for the salvation of the LORD.</item>
		<item>Psalm 84:5|Blessed is the man whose strength is in thee; in whose heart are the ways of them.</item>
		<item>Mark 14:38|Watch ye and pray, lest ye enter into temptation. The spirit truly is ready, but the flesh is weak.</item>
		<item>Romans 12:12|Rejoicing in hope; patient in tribulation; continuing instant in prayer.</item>
		<item>Matthew 8:7|And Jesus saith unto him, I will come and heal him.</item>
		<item>Matthew 10:33|But whosoever shall deny me before men, him will I also deny before my Father which is in heaven.</item>
		<item>Matthew 10:31|Fear ye not therefore, ye are of more value than many sparrows.</item>
		<item>Matthew 10:32|Whosoever therefore shall confess me before men, him will I confess also before my Father which is in heaven.</item>
		<item>Luke 18:27|And he said, The things which are impossible with men are possible with God.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 48:22|There is no peace, saith the LORD, unto the wicked.</item>
		<item>Psalm 25:14|The secret of the LORD is with them that fear him; and he will shew them his covenant.</item>
		<item>Matthew 18:11|For the Son of man is come to save that which was lost.</item>
		<item>Psalm 34:17|The righteous cry, and the LORD heareth, and delivereth them out of all their troubles.</item>
		<item>Luke 22:40|And when he was at the place, he said unto them, Pray that ye enter not into temptation.</item>
		<item>Romans 5:8|But God commendeth his love toward us, in that, while we were yet sinners, Christ died for us.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 26:7|The way of the just is uprightness: thou, most upright, dost weigh the path of the just.</item>
		<item>Job 5:18|For he maketh sore, and bindeth up: he woundeth, and his hands make whole.</item>
		<item>Job 5:10|Who giveth rain upon the earth, and sendeth waters upon the fields:</item>
		<item>Isaiah 42:18|Hear, ye deaf; and look, ye blind, that ye may see.</item>
		<item>Matthew 16:26|For what is a man profited, if he shall gain the whole world, and lose his own soul? or what shall a man give in exchange for his soul?</item>
		<item>Matthew 21:22|And all things, whatsoever ye shall ask in prayer, believing, ye shall receive.</item>
		<item>Matthew 22:29|He answered and said, I will not: but afterward he repented, and went.</item>
		<item>Matthew 5:48|Be ye therefore perfect, even as your Father which is in heaven is perfect.</item>
		<item>Psalm 147:7|Sing unto the LORD with thanksgiving; sing praise upon the harp unto our God:</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 16:14|Let all your things be done with charity.</item>
		<item>Psalms 103:14|For he knoweth our frame; he remembereth that we are dust.</item>
		<item>Psalm 126:5|They that sow in tears shall reap in joy.</item>
		<item>Job 15:11|Are the consolations of God small with thee?</item>
		<item>Psalms 118:8|It is better to trust in the LORD than to put confidence in man.</item>
		<item>Isaiah 50:8|He is near that justifieth me; who will contend with me? let us stand together: who is mine adversary? let him come near to me.</item>
		<item>Psalms 119:105|Thy word is a lamp unto my feet, and a light unto my path.</item>
		<item>Psalms 139:23–24|Search me, O God, and know my heart: try me, and know my thoughts: And see if there be any wicked way in me, and lead me in the way everlasting.</item>
		<item>Psalms 18:32|It is God that girdeth me with strength, and maketh my way perfect.</item>
		<item>II Corinthians 2:8|Wherefore I beseech you that ye would confirm your love toward him.</item>
		<item>Luke 21:33|Heaven and earth shall pass away: but my words shall not pass away.</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 16:13|Watch ye, stand fast in the faith, quit you like men, be strong.</item>
		<item>Jeremiah 7:8|Behold, ye trust in lying words, that cannot profit.</item>
		<item>Luke 14:34|Salt is good: but if the salt have lost his savour, wherewith shall it be seasoned?</item>
		<item>Matthew 5:8|Blessed are the pure in heart: for they shall see God.</item>
		<item>Matthew 6:33|But seek ye first the kingdom of God, and his righteousness; and all these things shall be added unto you.</item>
		<item>Matthew 5:9|Blessed are the peacemakers: for they shall be called the children of God.</item>
		<item>John 14:13,14|And whatsoever ye shall ask in my name, that will I do, that the Father may be glorified in the Son. If ye shall ask any thing in my name, I will do it.</item>
		<item>Matthew 28:20|Teaching them to observe all things whatsoever I have commanded you: and, lo, I am with you always, even unto the end of the world. Amen.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 10:22|The blessing of the LORD, it maketh rich, and he addeth no sorrow with it.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 14:1|Every wise woman buildeth her house: but the foolish plucketh it down with her hands.</item>
		<item>I Corinthians 16:9|For a great door and effectual is opened unto me, and there are many adversaries.</item>
		<item>Psalm 23:4|Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me; thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.</item>
		<item>I Peter 5:6|Humble yourselves therefore under the mighty hand of God, that he may exalt you in due time</item>
		<item>Romans 8:32|He that spared not his own Son, but delivered him up for us all, how shall he not with him also freely give us all things?</item>
		<item>Psalm 28:7|The LORD is my strength and my shield; my heart trusted in him, and I am helped: therefore my heart greatly rejoiceth; and with my song will I praise him.</item>
		<item>Mark 11:24|Therefore I say unto you, What things soever ye desire, when ye pray, believe that ye receive them, and ye shall have them.</item>
		<item>Hebrews 2:18|For in that he himself hath suffered being tempted, he is able to succour them that are tempted.</item>
		<item>Matthew 7:7–8|Ask, and it shall be given you; seek, and ye shall find; knock, and it shall be opened unto you: For every one that asketh receiveth; and he that seeketh findeth; and to him that knocketh it shall be opened.</item>
		<item>James 4:8|Draw nigh to God, and he will draw nigh to you. Cleanse your hands, ye sinners; and purify your hearts, ye double minded.</item>
		<item>John 8:12|Then spake Jesus again unto them, saying, I am the light of the world: he that followeth me shall not walk in darkness, but shall have the light of life.</item>
		<item>Proverbs 14:12|There is a way which seemeth right unto a man, but the end thereof are the ways of death.</item>
		<item>Psalms 34:13|Keep thy tongue from evil, and thy lips from speaking guile.</item>
		<item>Judas 24|Now unto him that is able to keep you from falling, and to present you faultless before the presence of his glory with exceeding joy.</item>
		<item>James 5:16|Confess your faults one to another, and pray one for another, that ye may be healed. The effectual fervent prayer of a righteous man availeth much.</item>
		<item>Philippians 4:7|And the peace of God, which passeth all understanding, shall keep your hearts and minds through Christ Jesus.</item>
		<item>John 15:7|If ye abide in me, and my words abide in you, ye shall ask what ye will, and it shall be done unto you.</item>
		<item>1 Corinthians 10:13|There hath no temptation taken you but such as is common to man: but God is faithful, who will not suffer you to be tempted above that ye are able; but will with the temptation also make a way to escape, that ye may be able to bear it.</item>
		<item>Psalm 34:7|The angel of the LORD encampeth round about them that fear him, and delivereth them.</item>
		<item>Psalm 34:8|O taste and see that the LORD is good: blessed is the man that trusteth in him.</item>
		<item>Psalm 37:16|A little that a righteous man hath is better than the riches of many wicked.</item>
		<item>Psalms 37:23|The steps of a good man are ordered by the LORD: and he delighteth in his way.</item>
		<item>Psalm 37:5|Commit thy way unto the LORD; trust also in him; and he shall bring it to pass.</item>
		<item>Psalm 40:1|I waited patiently for the LORD; and he inclined unto me, and heard my cry.</item>
		<item>Psalm 42:1|As the hart panteth after the water brooks, so panteth my soul after thee, O God.</item>
		<item>Psalms 46:1|God is our refuge and strength, a very present help in trouble.</item>
		<item>Psalms 46:10|Be still, and know that I am God</item>
		<item>Psalm 46:11|The LORD of hosts is with us; the God of Jacob is our refuge.</item>
		<item>Psalms 51:10|Create in me a clean heart, O God; and renew a right spirit within me.</item>
		<item>Psalm 91:1|He that dwelleth in the secret place of the most High shall abide under the shadow of the Almighty.</item>
		<item>Psalm 91:10–11|There shall no evil befall thee, neither shall any plague come nigh thy dwelling. For he shall give his angels charge over thee, to keep thee in all thy ways.</item>
		<item>Psalm 91:2|I will say of the LORD, He is my refuge and my fortress: my God; in him will I trust.</item>
		<item>Psalm 91:7|A thousand shall fall at thy side, and ten thousand at thy right hand; but it shall not come nigh thee.</item>
		<item>Zephaniah 3:17|The LORD thy God in the midst of thee is mighty; he will save, he will rejoice over thee with joy; he will rest in his love, he will joy over thee with singing.</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="situations_array">
        <item>anxious|&#8230;  anxious and impatient</item>
        <item>worried_money|&#8230;  worried with money</item>
        <item>afraid|&#8230;  afraid</item>
        <item>alone|&#8230;  alone</item>
        <item>suffering|&#8230;  suffering</item>
        <item>sick|&#8230;  sick</item>
        <item>terminal|&#8230;  facing a terminal situation</item>
        <item>death|&#8230;  suffering because of someone\'s death</item>
        <item>disaster|&#8230;  facing a total disaster</item>
        <item>travel|&#8230;  going to travel</item>
        <item>temptation|&#8230;  striving against temptation</item>
        <item>advices|&#8230;  looking for advices</item>
        <item>decisions|&#8230;  taking decisions</item>
        <item>angry|&#8230;  angry</item>
        <item>envy|&#8230;  feeling envy</item>
        <item>guilty|&#8230;  feeling guilty</item>
        <item>abandon|&#8230;  thinking God has abandoned you</item>
        <item>tired|&#8230;  tired and discoraged</item>
        <item>heaven|&#8230;  looking for heavens path</item>
        <item>pray|&#8230;  wanting to know how to pray</item>
        <item>thankful|&#8230;  thankful for God\'s blessings</item>        
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="anxious_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 37:3-5|
				3. Trust in the Lord, and do good; Dwell in the land, and feed on His faithfulness. \n
				4. Delight yourself also in the Lord, And He shall give you the desires of your heart. \n
				5. Commit your way to the Lord, Trust also in Him, And He shall bring it to pass.
		</item>
        <item>
            Matthew 6:25-34|
			    25. Therefore I say unto you, Take no thought for your life, what ye shall eat, or what ye shall drink; nor yet for your body, what ye shall put on. Is not the life more than meat, and the body than raiment?\n
				26. Behold the fowls of the air: for they sow not, neither do they reap, nor gather into barns; yet your heavenly Father feedeth them. Are ye not much better than they?\n
				27. Which of you by taking thought can add one cubit unto his stature?\n
				28. And why take ye thought for raiment? Consider the lilies of the field, how they grow; they toil not, neither do they spin:\n
				29. And yet I say unto you, That even Solomon in all his glory was not arrayed like one of these.\n
				30. Wherefore, if God so clothe the grass of the field, which to day is, and to morrow is cast into the oven, shall he not much more clothe you, O ye of little faith?\n
				31. Therefore take no thought, saying, What shall we eat? or, What shall we drink? or, Wherewithal shall we be clothed?\n
				32. (For after all these things do the Gentiles seek:) for your heavenly Father knoweth that ye have need of all these things.\n
				33. But seek ye first the kingdom of God, and his righteousness; and all these things shall be added unto you.\n
				34. Take therefore no thought for the morrow: for the morrow shall take thought for the things of itself. Sufficient unto the day is the evil thereof.
		</item>
        <item>
            Romans 5:3-5|
				3. And not only so, but we glory in tribulations also: knowing that tribulation worketh patience;\n
				4. And patience, experience; and experience, hope:\n
				5. And hope maketh not ashamed; because the love of God is shed abroad in our hearts by the Holy Ghost which is given unto us.
		</item>
        <item>
            Philippians 4:6-7|
				6. Be careful for nothing; but in every thing by prayer and supplication with thanksgiving let your requests be made known unto God.\n
				7. And the peace of God, which passeth all understanding, shall keep your hearts and minds through Christ Jesus.
 		</item>
        <item>
            James 5:7-11|
				7. Be patient therefore, brethren, unto the coming of the Lord. Behold, the husbandman waiteth for the precious fruit of the earth, and hath long patience for it, until he receive the early and latter rain.\n
 				8. Be ye also patient; stablish your hearts: for the coming of the Lord draweth nigh.\n
 				9. Grudge not one against another, brethren, lest ye be condemned: behold, the judge standeth before the door.\n
				10. Take, my brethren, the prophets, who have spoken in the name of the Lord, for an example of suffering affliction, and of patience.\n
				11. Behold, we count them happy which endure. Ye have heard of the patience of Job, and have seen the end of the Lord; that the Lord is very pitiful, and of tender mercy. 
		</item>
        <item>
            I Peter 5:6-7|
		     	6. Humble yourselves therefore under the mighty hand of God, that he may exalt you in due time:\n
 				7. Casting all your care upon him; for he careth for you.
		</item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="worried_money_array">
        <item>
            Eccleasiastes 5:10|
	        	10. He that loveth silver shall not be satisfied with silver; nor he that loveth abundance with increase: this is also vanity.
        </item>
        <item>
            Matthew 6:19-21|
		        19. Lay not up for yourselves treasures upon earth, where moth and rust doth corrupt, and where thieves break through and steal: \n
				20. But lay up for yourselves treasures in heaven, where neither moth nor rust doth corrupt, and where thieves do not break through nor steal: \n
				21. For where your treasure is, there will your heart be also. 
		</item>
        <item>
            I Timothy 6:6-10|
				6. But godliness with contentment is great gain.\n
				7. For we brought nothing into this world, and it is certain we can carry nothing out.\n
				8. And having food and raiment let us be therewith content.\n
				9. But they that will be rich fall into temptation and a snare, and into many foolish and hurtful lusts, which drown men in destruction and perdition.\n
				10. For the love of money is the root of all evil: which while some coveted after, they have erred from the faith, and pierced themselves through with many sorrows.
        </item>
        <item>
            Hebrews 13:5-6|
				5. Let your conversation be without covetousness; and be content with such things as ye have: for he hath said, I will never leave thee, nor forsake thee.\n
				6. So that we may boldly say, The Lord is my helper, and I will not fear what man shall do unto me.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="afraid_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 4:8|
           		8. I will both lay me down in peace, and sleep: for thou, LORD, only makest me dwell in safety.
        </item>
        <item>
            Isaiah 41:13|
            	13. For I the LORD thy God will hold thy right hand, saying unto thee, Fear not; I will help thee.
        </item>
        <item>
            Luke 8:22-25|
            	22. Now it came to pass on a certain day, that he went into a ship with his disciples: and he said unto them, Let us go over unto the other side of the lake. And they launched forth.\n
 				23. But as they sailed he fell asleep: and there came down a storm of wind on the lake; and they were filled with water, and were in jeopardy.\n
 				24. And they came to him, and awoke him, saying, Master, master, we perish. Then he arose, and rebuked the wind and the raging of the water: and they ceased, and there was a calm.\n
 				25. And he said unto them, Where is your faith? And they being afraid wondered, saying one to another, What manner of man is this! for he commandeth even the winds and water, and they obey him.
            </item>
        <item>
            John 14:27|
            	27. Peace I leave with you, my peace I give unto you: not as the world giveth, give I unto you. Let not your heart be troubled, neither let it be afraid.
            </item>
        <item>
            John 16:33|
            	33. These things I have spoken unto you, that in me ye might have peace. In the world ye shall have tribulation: but be of good cheer; I have overcome the world.
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 8:1|
             	1. There is therefore now no condemnation to them which are in Christ Jesus, who walk not after the flesh, but after the Spirit. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 8:31-39|
				31. What shall we then say to these things? If God be for us, who can be against us?\n
				32. He that spared not his own Son, but delivered him up for us all, how shall he not with him also freely give us all things?\n
				33. Who shall lay any thing to the charge of God\'s elect? It is God that justifieth.\n
				34. Who is he that condemneth? It is Christ that died, yea rather, that is risen again, who is even at the right hand of God, who also maketh intercession for us.\n
				35. Who shall separate us from the love of Christ? shall tribulation, or distress, or persecution, or famine, or nakedness, or peril, or sword?\n
				36. As it is written, For thy sake we are killed all the day long; we are accounted as sheep for the slaughter.\n
				37. Nay, in all these things we are more than conquerors through him that loved us.\n
				38. For I am persuaded, that neither death, nor life, nor angels, nor principalities, nor powers, nor things present, nor things to come,\n
				39. Nor height, nor depth, nor any other creature, shall be able to separate us from the love of God, which is in Christ Jesus our Lord.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="alone_array">
    	<item>
            Psalm 10:12-14|
            	12. Arise, O LORD; O God, lift up thine hand: forget not the humble.\n
				13. Wherefore doth the wicked contemn God? he hath said in his heart, Thou wilt not require it.\n
				14. Thou hast seen it; for thou beholdest mischief and spite, to requite it with thy hand: the poor committeth himself unto thee; thou art the helper of the fatherless.
        </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 25:16-18|
            	16. Turn thee unto me, and have mercy upon me; for I am desolate and afflicted.\n
 				17. The troubles of my heart are enlarged: O bring thou me out of my distresses.\n
				18. Look upon mine affliction and my pain; and forgive all my sins.
		</item>
        <item>
            Psalm 68:4-6|
            	4. Sing unto God, sing praises to his name: extol him that rideth upon the heavens by his name JAH, and rejoice before him.\n
 				5. A father of the fatherless, and a judge of the widows, is God in his holy habitation.\n
 				6. God setteth the solitary in families: he bringeth out those which are bound with chains: but the rebellious dwell in a dry land. 
        </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 146|
             	1. Praise ye the LORD. Praise the LORD, O my soul.\n
 				2. While I live will I praise the LORD: I will sing praises unto my God while I have any being.\n
 				3. Put not your trust in princes, nor in the son of man, in whom there is no help.\n
 				4. His breath goeth forth, he returneth to his earth; in that very day his thoughts perish.\n
 				5. Happy is he that hath the God of Jacob for his help, whose hope is in the LORD his God:\n
 				6. Which made heaven, and earth, the sea, and all that therein is: which keepeth truth for ever:\n
 				7. Which executeth judgment for the oppressed: which giveth food to the hungry. The LORD looseth the prisoners:\n
 				8. The LORD openeth the eyes of the blind: the LORD raiseth them that are bowed down: the LORD loveth the righteous:\n
 				9. The LORD preserveth the strangers; he relieveth the fatherless and widow: but the way of the wicked he turneth upside down.\n
 				10. The LORD shall reign for ever, even thy God, O Zion, unto all generations. Praise ye the LORD. 
        </item>
        <item>
            Matthew 28:20|
            	20. Teaching them to observe all things whatsoever I have commanded you: and, lo, I am with you always, even unto the end of the world. Amen.
        </item>
        <item>
            John 14:18-19|
             	18. I will not leave you comfortless: I will come to you.\n
 				19. Yet a little while, and the world seeth me no more; but ye see me: because I live, ye shall live also.
            </item>
        <item>
            I Peter 5:7|
             	7. Casting all your care upon him; for he careth for you.
        </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="suffering_array">
        <item>
            Matthew 5:4|
            	4. Blessed are they that mourn: for they shall be comforted. 
        </item>
        <item>
            Romans 8:31-39|
				31. What shall we then say to these things? If God be for us, who can be against us?\n
 				32. He that spared not his own Son, but delivered him up for us all, how shall he not with him also freely give us all things?\n
 				33. Who shall lay any thing to the charge of God\'s elect? It is God that justifieth.\n
 				34. Who is he that condemneth? It is Christ that died, yea rather, that is risen again, who is even at the right hand of God, who also maketh intercession for us.\n
 				35. Who shall separate us from the love of Christ? shall tribulation, or distress, or persecution, or famine, or nakedness, or peril, or sword?\n
 				36. As it is written, For thy sake we are killed all the day long; we are accounted as sheep for the slaughter.\n
 				37. Nay, in all these things we are more than conquerors through him that loved us.\n
 				38. For I am persuaded, that neither death, nor life, nor angels, nor principalities, nor powers, nor things present, nor things to come,\n
 				39. Nor height, nor depth, nor any other creature, shall be able to separate us from the love of God, which is in Christ Jesus our Lord.
        </item>
        <item>
            II Corinthians 1:3-6|
				3. Blessed be God, even the Father of our Lord Jesus Christ, the Father of mercies, and the God of all comfort;\n
 				4. Who comforteth us in all our tribulation, that we may be able to comfort them which are in any trouble, by the comfort wherewith we ourselves are comforted of God.\n
 				5. For as the sufferings of Christ abound in us, so our consolation also aboundeth by Christ.\n
 				6. And whether we be afflicted, it is for your consolation and salvation, which is effectual in the enduring of the same sufferings which we also suffer: or whether we be comforted, it is for your consolation and salvation.
           </item>
        <item>
            II Corinthians 4:16-18|
            	16. For which cause we faint not; but though our outward man perish, yet the inward man is renewed day by day.\n
 				17. For our light affliction, which is but for a moment, worketh for us a far more exceeding and eternal weight of glory;\n
				18. While we look not at the things which are seen, but at the things which are not seen: for the things which are seen are temporal; but the things which are not seen are eternal.
            </item>
        <item>
            II Corinthians 12:7-10|
				7. And lest I should be exalted above measure through the abundance of the revelations, there was given to me a thorn in the flesh, the messenger of Satan to buffet me, lest I should be exalted above measure.\n
				8. For this thing I besought the Lord thrice, that it might depart from me.\n
				9. And he said unto me, My grace is sufficient for thee: for my strength is made perfect in weakness. Most gladly therefore will I rather glory in my infirmities, that the power of Christ may rest upon me.\n
				10. Therefore I take pleasure in infirmities, in reproaches, in necessities, in persecutions, in distresses for Christ\'s sake: for when I am weak, then am I strong.
            </item>
        <item>
            James 1:2-4|
             	2. My brethren, count it all joy when ye fall into divers temptations;\n
 				3. Knowing this, that the trying of your faith worketh patience.\n
 				4. But let patience have her perfect work, that ye may be perfect and entire, wanting nothing.
            </item>
        <item>
            Revelation 2:10|
            	10. Fear none of those things which thou shalt suffer: behold, the devil shall cast some of you into prison, that ye may be tried; and ye shall have tribulation ten days: be thou faithful unto death, and I will give thee a crown of life.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="sick_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 41:1-3|
             	1. Blessed is he that considereth the poor: the LORD will deliver him in time of trouble.\n
 				2. The LORD will preserve him, and keep him alive; and he shall be blessed upon the earth: and thou wilt not deliver him unto the will of his enemies.\n
 				3. The LORD will strengthen him upon the bed of languishing: thou wilt make all his bed in his sickness.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 68:19-20|
             	19. Blessed be the Lord, who daily loadeth us with benefits, even the God of our salvation. Selah.\n
 				20. He that is our God is the God of salvation; and unto GOD the Lord belong the issues from death.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 103:1-5|
             	1. Bless the LORD, O my soul: and all that is within me, bless his holy name.\n
 				2. Bless the LORD, O my soul, and forget not all his benefits:\n
				3. Who forgiveth all thine iniquities; who healeth all thy diseases;\n
				4. Who redeemeth thy life from destruction; who crowneth thee with lovingkindness and tender mercies;\n
				5. Who satisfieth thy mouth with good things; so that thy youth is renewed like the eagle\'s.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 146|
				1. Praise ye the LORD. Praise the LORD, O my soul.\n
				2. While I live will I praise the LORD: I will sing praises unto my God while I have any being.\n
				3. Put not your trust in princes, nor in the son of man, in whom there is no help.\n
				4. His breath goeth forth, he returneth to his earth; in that very day his thoughts perish.\n
				5. Happy is he that hath the God of Jacob for his help, whose hope is in the LORD his God:\n
				6. Which made heaven, and earth, the sea, and all that therein is: which keepeth truth for ever:\n
				7. Which executeth judgment for the oppressed: which giveth food to the hungry. The LORD looseth the prisoners:\n
				8. The LORD openeth the eyes of the blind: the LORD raiseth them that are bowed down: the LORD loveth the righteous:\n
				9. The LORD preserveth the strangers; he relieveth the fatherless and widow: but the way of the wicked he turneth upside down.\n
				10. The LORD shall reign for ever, even thy God, O Zion, unto all generations. Praise ye the LORD.
            </item>
        <item>
            Isaiah 54:10|
            	10. For the mountains shall depart, and the hills be removed; but my kindness shall not depart from thee, neither shall the covenant of my peace be removed, saith the LORD that hath mercy on thee. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 5:1-5|
            	1. Therefore being justified by faith, we have peace with God through our Lord Jesus Christ:\n
				2. By whom also we have access by faith into this grace wherein we stand, and rejoice in hope of the glory of God.\n
				3. And not only so, but we glory in tribulations also: knowing that tribulation worketh patience;\n
				4. And patience, experience; and experience, hope:\n
				5. And hope maketh not ashamed; because the love of God is shed abroad in our hearts by the Holy Ghost which is given unto us.
            </item>
        <item>
            James 5:14-15|
            	14. Is any sick among you? let him call for the elders of the church; and let them pray over him, anointing him with oil in the name of the Lord:\n
 				15. And the prayer of faith shall save the sick, and the Lord shall raise him up; and if he have committed sins, they shall be forgiven him.
            </item>
        <item>
            I Peter 5:10-11|
            	10. But the God of all grace, who hath called us unto his eternal glory by Christ Jesus, after that ye have suffered a while, make you perfect, stablish, strengthen, settle you.\n
 				11. To him be glory and dominion for ever and ever. Amen.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="terminal_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 23|
	            1. The LORD is my shepherd; I shall not want.\n
				2. He maketh me to lie down in green pastures: he leadeth me beside the still waters.\n
				3. He restoreth my soul: he leadeth me in the paths of righteousness for his name\'s sake.\n
				4. Yea, though I walk through the valley of the shadow of death, I will fear no evil: for thou art with me; thy rod and thy staff they comfort me.\n
				5. Thou preparest a table before me in the presence of mine enemies: thou anointest my head with oil; my cup runneth over.\n
				6. Surely goodness and mercy shall follow me all the days of my life: and I will dwell in the house of the LORD for ever. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 8:18-30|
				18. For I reckon that the sufferings of this present time are not worthy to be compared with the glory which shall be revealed in us.\n
 				19. For the earnest expectation of the creature waiteth for the manifestation of the sons of God.\n
 				20. For the creature was made subject to vanity, not willingly, but by reason of him who hath subjected the same in hope,\n
 				21. Because the creature itself also shall be delivered from the bondage of corruption into the glorious liberty of the children of God.\n
 				22. For we know that the whole creation groaneth and travaileth in pain together until now.\n
				23. And not only they, but ourselves also, which have the firstfruits of the Spirit, even we ourselves groan within ourselves, waiting for the adoption, to wit, the redemption of our body.\n
				24. For we are saved by hope: but hope that is seen is not hope: for what a man seeth, why doth he yet hope for?\n
				25. But if we hope for that we see not, then do we with patience wait for it.\n
				26. Likewise the Spirit also helpeth our infirmities: for we know not what we should pray for as we ought: but the Spirit itself maketh intercession for us with groanings which cannot be uttered.\n
				27. And he that searcheth the hearts knoweth what is the mind of the Spirit, because he maketh intercession for the saints according to the will of God.\n
				28. And we know that all things work together for good to them that love God, to them who are the called according to his purpose.\n
				29. For whom he did foreknow, he also did predestinate to be conformed to the image of his Son, that he might be the firstborn among many brethren.\n
				30. Moreover whom he did predestinate, them he also called: and whom he called, them he also justified: and whom he justified, them he also glorified.
            </item>
        <item>
            II Corinthians 5:1-10|
				1. For we know that if our earthly house of this tabernacle were dissolved, we have a building of God, an house not made with hands, eternal in the heavens.\n
			 	2. For in this we groan, earnestly desiring to be clothed upon with our house which is from heaven:\n
				3. If so be that being clothed we shall not be found naked.\n
				4. For we that are in this tabernacle do groan, being burdened: not for that we would be unclothed, but clothed upon, that mortality might be swallowed up of life.\n
		 		5. Now he that hath wrought us for the selfsame thing is God, who also hath given unto us the earnest of the Spirit.\n
			 	6. Therefore we are always confident, knowing that, whilst we are at home in the body, we are absent from the Lord:\n
			 	7. (For we walk by faith, not by sight:)\n
			 	8. We are confident, I say, and willing rather to be absent from the body, and to be present with the Lord.\n
			 	9. Wherefore we labour, that, whether present or absent, we may be accepted of him.\n
			 	10. For we must all appear before the judgment seat of Christ; that every one may receive the things done in his body, according to that he hath done, whether it be good or bad. 
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="death_array">
        <item>
            John 11:25-26|
				25. Jesus said unto her, I am the resurrection, and the life: he that believeth in me, though he were dead, yet shall he live:\n
 				26. And whosoever liveth and believeth in me shall never die. Believest thou this?
            </item>
        <item>
            I Corinthians 15:50-58|
	            50. Now this I say, brethren, that flesh and blood cannot inherit the kingdom of God; neither doth corruption inherit incorruption.\n
				51. Behold, I shew you a mystery; We shall not all sleep, but we shall all be changed,\n
				52. In a moment, in the twinkling of an eye, at the last trump: for the trumpet shall sound, and the dead shall be raised incorruptible, and we shall be changed.\n
				53. For this corruptible must put on incorruption, and this mortal must put on immortality.\n
				54. So when this corruptible shall have put on incorruption, and this mortal shall have put on immortality, then shall be brought to pass the saying that is written, Death is swallowed up in victory.\n
				55. O death, where is thy sting? O grave, where is thy victory?\n
				56. The sting of death is sin; and the strength of sin is the law.\n
				57. But thanks be to God, which giveth us the victory through our Lord Jesus Christ.\n
				58. Therefore, my beloved brethren, be ye stedfast, unmoveable, always abounding in the work of the Lord, forasmuch as ye know that your labour is not in vain in the Lord. 
            </item>
        <item
            >I Thessalonians 4:13-18|
				13. But I would not have you to be ignorant, brethren, concerning them which are asleep, that ye sorrow not, even as others which have no hope.\n
			 	14. For if we believe that Jesus died and rose again, even so them also which sleep in Jesus will God bring with him.\n
			 	15. For this we say unto you by the word of the Lord, that we which are alive and remain unto the coming of the Lord shall not prevent them which are asleep.\n
			 	16. For the Lord himself shall descend from heaven with a shout, with the voice of the archangel, and with the trump of God: and the dead in Christ shall rise first:\n
			 	17. Then we which are alive and remain shall be caught up together with them in the clouds, to meet the Lord in the air: and so shall we ever be with the Lord.\n
			 	18. Wherefore comfort one another with these words.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="disaster_array">
        <item>
            Job 1:13-22|
           		13. And there was a day when his sons and his daughters were eating and drinking wine in their eldest brother\'s house:\n
			 	14. And there came a messenger unto Job, and said, The oxen were plowing, and the asses feeding beside them:\n
			 	15. And the Sabeans fell upon them, and took them away; yea, they have slain the servants with the edge of the sword; and I only am escaped alone to tell thee.\n
			 	16. While he was yet speaking, there came also another, and said, The fire of God is fallen from heaven, and hath burned up the sheep, and the servants, and consumed them; and I only am escaped alone to tell thee.\n
				17. While he was yet speaking, there came also another, and said, The Chaldeans made out three bands, and fell upon the camels, and have carried them away, yea, and slain the servants with the edge of the sword; and I only am escaped alone to tell thee.\n
				18. While he was yet speaking, there came also another, and said, Thy sons and thy daughters were eating and drinking wine in their eldest brother\'s house:\n
				19. And, behold, there came a great wind from the wilderness, and smote the four corners of the house, and it fell upon the young men, and they are dead; and I only am escaped alone to tell thee.\n
				20. Then Job arose, and rent his mantle, and shaved his head, and fell down upon the ground, and worshipped,\n
				21. And said, Naked came I out of my mother\'s womb, and naked shall I return thither: the LORD gave, and the LORD hath taken away; blessed be the name of the LORD.\n
				22. In all this Job sinned not, nor charged God foolishly.
            </item>
        <item>
            Isaiah 55:8-9|
				 8. For my thoughts are not your thoughts, neither are your ways my ways, saith the LORD.\n
				 9. For as the heavens are higher than the earth, so are my ways higher than your ways, and my thoughts than your thoughts. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 8:28|
           		28. And we know that all things work together for good to them that love God, to them who are the called according to his purpose. 
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="travel_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 46.1-3|
             	1. God is our refuge and strength, a very present help in trouble.\n
			 	2. Therefore will not we fear, though the earth be removed, and though the mountains be carried into the midst of the sea;\n
			 	3. Though the waters thereof roar and be troubled, though the mountains shake with the swelling thereof. Selah. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 91.1-6,14-16|
				 1. He that dwelleth in the secret place of the most High shall abide under the shadow of the Almighty.\n
				 2. I will say of the LORD, He is my refuge and my fortress: my God; in him will I trust.\n
				 3. Surely he shall deliver thee from the snare of the fowler, and from the noisome pestilence.\n
				 4. He shall cover thee with his feathers, and under his wings shalt thou trust: his truth shall be thy shield and buckler.\n
				 5. Thou shalt not be afraid for the terror by night; nor for the arrow that flieth by day;\n
				 6. Nor for the pestilence that walketh in darkness; nor for the destruction that wasteth at noonday.\n
				 14. Because he hath set his love upon me, therefore will I deliver him: I will set him on high, because he hath known my name.\n
				 15. He shall call upon me, and I will answer him: I will be with him in trouble; I will deliver him, and honour him.\n
				 16. With long life will I satisfy him, and shew him my salvation.
           </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 121|
				 1. I will lift up mine eyes unto the hills, from whence cometh my help.\n
				 2. My help cometh from the LORD, which made heaven and earth.\n
				 3. He will not suffer thy foot to be moved: he that keepeth thee will not slumber.\n
				 4. Behold, he that keepeth Israel shall neither slumber nor sleep.\n
				 5. The LORD is thy keeper: the LORD is thy shade upon thy right hand.\n
				 6. The sun shall not smite thee by day, nor the moon by night.\n
				 7. The LORD shall preserve thee from all evil: he shall preserve thy soul.\n
				 8. The LORD shall preserve thy going out and thy coming in from this time forth, and even for evermore.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="temptation_array">
        <item>
            Romans 12:1-2|
             	1. I beseech you therefore, brethren, by the mercies of God, that ye present your bodies a living sacrifice, holy, acceptable unto God, which is your reasonable service.\n
 				2. And be not conformed to this world: but be ye transformed by the renewing of your mind, that ye may prove what is that good, and acceptable, and perfect, will of God. 
            </item>
        <item>
            I Corinthians 10:12-13|
            	12. Aquele, pois, que cuida estar em pé, olhe não caia.\n
				13. Não veio sobre vós tentação, senão humana; mas fiel é Deus, que não vos deixará tentar acima do que podeis, antes com a tentação dará também o escape, para que a possais suportar. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Hebrews 2:17-18|
             	17. Wherefore in all things it behoved him to be made like unto his brethren, that he might be a merciful and faithful high priest in things pertaining to God, to make reconciliation for the sins of the people.\n
 				18. For in that he himself hath suffered being tempted, he is able to succour them that are tempted. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Hebrews 4:14-16|
            	14. Seeing then that we have a great high priest, that is passed into the heavens, Jesus the Son of God, let us hold fast our profession.\n
				15. For we have not an high priest which cannot be touched with the feeling of our infirmities; but was in all points tempted like as we are, yet without sin.\n
 				16. Let us therefore come boldly unto the throne of grace, that we may obtain mercy, and find grace to help in time of need. 
            </item>
        <item>
            James 1:12-15|
				12. Blessed is the man that endureth temptation: for when he is tried, he shall receive the crown of life, which the Lord hath promised to them that love him.\n
 				13. Let no man say when he is tempted, I am tempted of God: for God cannot be tempted with evil, neither tempteth he any man:\n
 				14. But every man is tempted, when he is drawn away of his own lust, and enticed.\n
 				15. Then when lust hath conceived, it bringeth forth sin: and sin, when it is finished, bringeth forth death.
            </item>
        <item>
            James 4:7|
             	7. Submit yourselves therefore to God. Resist the devil, and he will flee from you.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="advices_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 16|
             	1. Preserve me, O God: for in thee do I put my trust.\n
 				2. O my soul, thou hast said unto the LORD, Thou art my Lord: my goodness extendeth not to thee;\n
 				3. But to the saints that are in the earth, and to the excellent, in whom is all my delight.\n
 				4. Their sorrows shall be multiplied that hasten after another god: their drink offerings of blood will I not offer, nor take up their names into my lips.\n
 				5. The LORD is the portion of mine inheritance and of my cup: thou maintainest my lot.\n
 				6. The lines are fallen unto me in pleasant places; yea, I have a goodly heritage.\n
 				7. I will bless the LORD, who hath given me counsel: my reins also instruct me in the night seasons.\n
 				8. I have set the LORD always before me: because he is at my right hand, I shall not be moved.\n
 				9. Therefore my heart is glad, and my glory rejoiceth: my flesh also shall rest in hope.\n
 				10. For thou wilt not leave my soul in hell; neither wilt thou suffer thine Holy One to see corruption.\n
 				11. Thou wilt shew me the path of life: in thy presence is fulness of joy; at thy right hand there are 
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 25:4-10|
             	4. Shew me thy ways, O LORD; teach me thy paths.\n
 				5. Lead me in thy truth, and teach me: for thou art the God of my salvation; on thee do I wait all the day.\n
 				6. Remember, O LORD, thy tender mercies and thy lovingkindnesses; for they have been ever of old.\n
 				7. Remember not the sins of my youth, nor my transgressions: according to thy mercy remember thou me for thy goodness\' sake, O LORD.\n
 				8. Good and upright is the LORD: therefore will he teach sinners in the way.\n
 				9. The meek will he guide in judgment: and the meek will he teach his way.\n
 				10. All the paths of the LORD are mercy and truth unto such as keep his covenant and his testimonies.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 32:8|
             	8. I will instruct thee and teach thee in the way which thou shalt go: I will guide thee with mine eye. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 119:105|
            	105. Thy word is a lamp unto my feet, and a light unto my path. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Isaiah 30:21|
            	21. E os teus ouvidos ouvirão a palavra do que está por detrás de ti, dizendo: Este é o caminho, andai nele, sem vos desviardes nem para a direita nem para a esquerda. 
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="decisions_array">
        <item>
            Proverbs 3:5-6|
            	5. Trust in the LORD with all thine heart; and lean not unto thine own understanding.\n
 				6. In all thy ways acknowledge him, and he shall direct thy paths.
            </item>
        <item>
            Proverbs 16:3|
            	3. Commit thy works unto the LORD, and thy thoughts shall be established.
            </item>
        <item>
            I Corinthians 10:31|
            	31. Whether therefore ye eat, or drink, or whatsoever ye do, do all to the glory of God.
            </item>
        <item>
            Galatians 6:10|
            	10. As we have therefore opportunity, let us do good unto all men, especially unto them who are of the household of faith.
            </item>
        <item>
            James 1:5-8|
             	5. If any of you lack wisdom, let him ask of God, that giveth to all men liberally, and upbraideth not; and it shall be given him.\n
 				6. But let him ask in faith, nothing wavering. For he that wavereth is like a wave of the sea driven with the wind and tossed.\n
 				7. For let not that man think that he shall receive any thing of the Lord.\n
 				8. A double minded man is unstable in all his ways.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="angry_array">
        <item>
            Matthew 5:44-48|
	            44. But I say unto you, Love your enemies, bless them that curse you, do good to them that hate you, and pray for them which despitefully use you, and persecute you;\n
				45. That ye may be the children of your Father which is in heaven: for he maketh his sun to rise on the evil and on the good, and sendeth rain on the just and on the unjust.\n
				46. For if ye love them which love you, what reward have ye? do not even the publicans the same?\n
				47. And if ye salute your brethren only, what do ye more than others? do not even the publicans so?\n
				48. Be ye therefore perfect, even as your Father which is in heaven is perfect.
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 12:17-21|
            	17. Recompense to no man evil for evil. Provide things honest in the sight of all men.\n
				 18. If it be possible, as much as lieth in you, live peaceably with all men.\n
				 19. Dearly beloved, avenge not yourselves, but rather give place unto wrath: for it is written, Vengeance is mine; I will repay, saith the Lord.\n
				 20. Therefore if thine enemy hunger, feed him; if he thirst, give him drink: for in so doing thou shalt heap coals of fire on his head.\n
				 21. Be not overcome of evil, but overcome evil with good.
            </item>
        <item>
            I Corinthians 13|
	             1. Though I speak with the tongues of men and of angels, and have not charity, I am become as sounding brass, or a tinkling cymbal.\n
				 2. And though I have the gift of prophecy, and understand all mysteries, and all knowledge; and though I have all faith, so that I could remove mountains, and have not charity, I am nothing.\n
				 3. And though I bestow all my goods to feed the poor, and though I give my body to be burned, and have not charity, it profiteth me nothing.\n
				 4. Charity suffereth long, and is kind; charity envieth not; charity vaunteth not itself, is not puffed up,\n
				 5. Doth not behave itself unseemly, seeketh not her own, is not easily provoked, thinketh no evil;\n
				 6. Rejoiceth not in iniquity, but rejoiceth in the truth;\n
				 7. Beareth all things, believeth all things, hopeth all things, endureth all things.\n
				 8. Charity never faileth: but whether there be prophecies, they shall fail; whether there be tongues, they shall cease; whether there be knowledge, it shall vanish away.\n
				 9. For we know in part, and we prophesy in part.\n
				 10. But when that which is perfect is come, then that which is in part shall be done away.\n
				 11. When I was a child, I spake as a child, I understood as a child, I thought as a child: but when I became a man, I put away childish things.\n
				 12. For now we see through a glass, darkly; but then face to face: now I know in part; but then shall I know even as also I am known.\n
				 13. And now abideth faith, hope, charity, these three; but the greatest of these is charity.
            </item>
        <item>
            Colossians 3:12-17|
	            12. Revesti-vos, pois, como eleitos de Deus, santos e amados, de entranhas de misericórdia, de benignidade, humildade, mansidão, longanimidade;\n
				13. Suportando-vos uns aos outros, e perdoando-vos uns aos outros, se alguém tiver queixa contra outro; assim como Cristo vos perdoou, assim fazei vós também.\n
				14. E, sobre tudo isto, revesti-vos de amor, que é o vínculo da perfeição.\n
				15. E a paz de Deus, para a qual também fostes chamados em um corpo, domine em vossos corações; e sede agradecidos.\n
				16. A palavra de Cristo habite em vós abundantemente, em toda a sabedoria, ensinando-vos e admoestando-vos uns aos outros, com Psalms, hinos e cânticos espirituais, cantando ao Senhor com graça em vosso coração.\n
				17. E, quanto fizerdes por palavras ou por obras, fazei tudo em nome do Senhor Jesus, dando por ele graças a Deus Pai.
            </item>
        <item>
            James 1:19-20|
             	19. Wherefore, my beloved brethren, let every man be swift to hear, slow to speak, slow to wrath:\n
				20. For the wrath of man worketh not the righteousness of God. 
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="envy_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 49:16-20|
				16. Be not thou afraid when one is made rich, when the glory of his house is increased;\n
			 	17. For when he dieth he shall carry nothing away: his glory shall not descend after him.\n
			 	18. Though while he lived he blessed his soul: and men will praise thee, when thou doest well to thyself.\n
			 	19. He shall go to the generation of his fathers; they shall never see light.\n
			 	20. Man that is in honour, and understandeth not, is like the beasts that perish.
            </item>
        <item>
            James 3:13-18|
            	13. Who is a wise man and endued with knowledge among you? let him shew out of a good conversation his works with meekness of wisdom.\n
			 	14. But if ye have bitter envying and strife in your hearts, glory not, and lie not against the truth.\n
			 	15. This wisdom descendeth not from above, but is earthly, sensual, devilish.\n
			 	16. For where envying and strife is, there is confusion and every evil work.\n
			 	17. But the wisdom that is from above is first pure, then peaceable, gentle, and easy to be intreated, full of mercy and good fruits, without partiality, and without hypocrisy.\n
			 	18. And the fruit of righteousness is sown in peace of them that make peace.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="guilty_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 32|
				1. Blessed is he whose transgression is forgiven, whose sin is covered.\n
			 	2. Blessed is the man unto whom the LORD imputeth not iniquity, and in whose spirit there is no guile.\n
			 	3. When I kept silence, my bones waxed old through my roaring all the day long.\n
			 	4. For day and night thy hand was heavy upon me: my moisture is turned into the drought of summer. Selah.\n
		 		5. I acknowledge my sin unto thee, and mine iniquity have I not hid. I said, I will confess my transgressions unto the LORD; and thou forgavest the iniquity of my sin. Selah.\n
			 	6. For this shall every one that is godly pray unto thee in a time when thou mayest be found: surely in the floods of great waters they shall not come nigh unto him.\n
		 		7. Thou art my hiding place; thou shalt preserve me from trouble; thou shalt compass me about with songs of deliverance. Selah.\n
			 	8. I will instruct thee and teach thee in the way which thou shalt go: I will guide thee with mine eye.\n
			 	9. Be ye not as the horse, or as the mule, which have no understanding: whose mouth must be held in with bit and bridle, lest they come near unto thee.\n
			 	10. Many sorrows shall be to the wicked: but he that trusteth in the LORD, mercy shall compass him about.\n
			 	11. Be glad in the LORD, and rejoice, ye righteous: and shout for joy, all ye that are upright in heart. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 51|
				1. Have mercy upon me, O God, according to thy lovingkindness: according unto the multitude of thy tender mercies blot out my transgressions.\n
				 2. Wash me throughly from mine iniquity, and cleanse me from my sin.\n
				 3. For I acknowledge my transgressions: and my sin is ever before me.\n
				 4. Against thee, thee only, have I sinned, and done this evil in thy sight: that thou mightest be justified when thou speakest, and be clear when thou judgest.\n
				 5. Behold, I was shapen in iniquity; and in sin did my mother conceive me.\n
				 6. Behold, thou desirest truth in the inward parts: and in the hidden part thou shalt make me to know wisdom.\n
				 7. Purge me with hyssop, and I shall be clean: wash me, and I shall be whiter than snow.\n
				 8. Make me to hear joy and gladness; that the bones which thou hast broken may rejoice.\n
				 9. Hide thy face from my sins, and blot out all mine iniquities.\n
				 10. Create in me a clean heart, O God; and renew a right spirit within me.\n
				 11. Cast me not away from thy presence; and take not thy holy spirit from me.\n
				 12. Restore unto me the joy of thy salvation; and uphold me with thy free spirit.\n
				 13. Then will I teach transgressors thy ways; and sinners shall be converted unto thee.\n
				 14. Deliver me from bloodguiltiness, O God, thou God of my salvation: and my tongue shall sing aloud of thy righteousness.\n
				 15. O Lord, open thou my lips; and my mouth shall shew forth thy praise.\n
				 16. For thou desirest not sacrifice; else would I give it: thou delightest not in burnt offering.\n
				 17. The sacrifices of God are a broken spirit: a broken and a contrite heart, O God, thou wilt not despise.\n
				 18. Do good in thy good pleasure unto Zion: build thou the walls of Jerusalem.\n
				 19. Then shalt thou be pleased with the sacrifices of righteousness, with burnt offering and whole burnt offering: then shall they offer bullocks upon thine altar.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 130|
				1. Out of the depths have I cried unto thee, O LORD.\n
				 2. Lord, hear my voice: let thine ears be attentive to the voice of my supplications.\n
				 3. If thou, LORD, shouldest mark iniquities, O Lord, who shall stand?\n
				 4. But there is forgiveness with thee, that thou mayest be feared.\n
				 5. I wait for the LORD, my soul doth wait, and in his word do I hope.\n
				 6. My soul waiteth for the Lord more than they that watch for the morning: I say, more than they that watch for the morning.\n
				 7. Let Israel hope in the LORD: for with the LORD there is mercy, and with him is plenteous redemption.\n
				 8. And he shall redeem Israel from all his iniquities.
            </item>
        <item>
            Isaiah 1:18|
            	18. Come now, and let us reason together, saith the LORD: though your sins be as scarlet, they shall be as white as snow; though they be red like crimson, they shall be as wool. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Luke 15|
	            1. Then drew near unto him all the publicans and sinners for to hear him.\n
				 2. And the Pharisees and scribes murmured, saying, This man receiveth sinners, and eateth with them.\n
				 3. And he spake this parable unto them, saying,\n
				 4. What man of you, having an hundred sheep, if he lose one of them, doth not leave the ninety and nine in the wilderness, and go after that which is lost, until he find it?\n
				 5. And when he hath found it, he layeth it on his shoulders, rejoicing.\n
				 6. And when he cometh home, he calleth together his friends and neighbours, saying unto them, Rejoice with me; for I have found my sheep which was lost.\n
				 7. I say unto you, that likewise joy shall be in heaven over one sinner that repenteth, more than over ninety and nine just persons, which need no repentance.\n
				 8. Either what woman having ten pieces of silver, if she lose one piece, doth not light a candle, and sweep the house, and seek diligently till she find it?\n
				 9. And when she hath found it, she calleth her friends and her neighbours together, saying, Rejoice with me; for I have found the piece which I had lost.\n
				 10. Likewise, I say unto you, there is joy in the presence of the angels of God over one sinner that repenteth.\n
				 11. And he said, A certain man had two sons:\n
				 12. And the younger of them said to his father, Father, give me the portion of goods that falleth to me. And he divided unto them his living.\n
				 13. And not many days after the younger son gathered all together, and took his journey into a far country, and there wasted his substance with riotous living.\n
				 14. And when he had spent all, there arose a mighty famine in that land; and he began to be in want.\n
				 15. And he went and joined himself to a citizen of that country; and he sent him into his fields to feed swine.\n
				 16. And he would fain have filled his belly with the husks that the swine did eat: and no man gave unto him.\n
				 17. And when he came to himself, he said, How many hired servants of my father\'s have bread enough and to spare, and I perish with hunger!\n
				 18. I will arise and go to my father, and will say unto him, Father, I have sinned against heaven, and before thee,\n
				 19. And am no more worthy to be called thy son: make me as one of thy hired servants.\n
				 20. And he arose, and came to his father. But when he was yet a great way off, his father saw him, and had compassion, and ran, and fell on his neck, and kissed him.\n
				 21. And the son said unto him, Father, I have sinned against heaven, and in thy sight, and am no more worthy to be called thy son.\n
				 22. But the father said to his servants, Bring forth the best robe, and put it on him; and put a ring on his hand, and shoes on his feet:\n
				 23. And bring hither the fatted calf, and kill it; and let us eat, and be merry:\n
				 24. For this my son was dead, and is alive again; he was lost, and is found. And they began to be merry.\n
				 25. Now his elder son was in the field: and as he came and drew nigh to the house, he heard musick and dancing.\n
				 26. And he called one of the servants, and asked what these things meant.\n
				 27. And he said unto him, Thy brother is come; and thy father hath killed the fatted calf, because he hath received him safe and sound.\n
				 28. And he was angry, and would not go in: therefore came his father out, and intreated him.\n
				 29. And he answering said to his father, Lo, these many years do I serve thee, neither transgressed I at any time thy commandment: and yet thou never gavest me a kid, that I might make merry with my friends:\n
				 30. But as soon as this thy son was come, which hath devoured thy living with harlots, thou hast killed for him the fatted calf.\n
				 31. And he said unto him, Son, thou art ever with me, and all that I have is thine.\n
				 32. It was meet that we should make merry, and be glad: for this thy brother was dead, and is alive again; and was lost, and is found.
            </item>
        <item>
            John 6:37|
            	37. All that the Father giveth me shall come to me; and him that cometh to me I will in no wise cast out.
            </item>
        <item>
            I John 1:8|
            	8. If we say that we have no sin, we deceive ourselves, and the truth is not in us. 
            </item>
        <item>
            I John 2:2|
            	2. And he is the propitiation for our sins: and not for ours only, but also for the sins of the whole world.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="abandon_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 22:1-11|
				1. My God, my God, why hast thou forsaken me? why art thou so far from helping me, and from the words of my roaring?\n
				 2. O my God, I cry in the day time, but thou hearest not; and in the night season, and am not silent.\n
				 3. But thou art holy, O thou that inhabitest the praises of Israel.\n
				 4. Our fathers trusted in thee: they trusted, and thou didst deliver them.\n
				 5. They cried unto thee, and were delivered: they trusted in thee, and were not confounded.\n
				 6. But I am a worm, and no man; a reproach of men, and despised of the people.\n
				 7. All they that see me laugh me to scorn: they shoot out the lip, they shake the head, saying,\n
				 8. He trusted on the LORD that he would deliver him: let him deliver him, seeing he delighted in him.\n
				 9. But thou art he that took me out of the womb: thou didst make me hope when I was upon my mother\'s breasts.\n
				 10. I was cast upon thee from the womb: thou art my God from my mother\'s belly.\n
				 11. Be not far from me; for trouble is near; for there is none to help.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 139:1-12|
				1. O lord, thou hast searched me, and known me.\n
				 2. Thou knowest my downsitting and mine uprising, thou understandest my thought afar off.\n
				 3. Thou compassest my path and my lying down, and art acquainted with all my ways.\n
				 4. For there is not a word in my tongue, but, lo, O LORD, thou knowest it altogether.\n
				 5. Thou hast beset me behind and before, and laid thine hand upon me.\n
				 6. Such knowledge is too wonderful for me; it is high, I cannot attain unto it.\n
				 7. Whither shall I go from thy spirit? or whither shall I flee from thy presence?\n
				 8. If I ascend up into heaven, thou art there: if I make my bed in hell, behold, thou art there.\n
				 9. If I take the wings of the morning, and dwell in the uttermost parts of the sea;\n
				 10. Even there shall thy hand lead me, and thy right hand shall hold me.\n
				 11. If I say, Surely the darkness shall cover me; even the night shall be light about me.\n
				 12. Yea, the darkness hideth not from thee; but the night shineth as the day: the darkness and the light are both alike to thee.
            </item>
        <item>
            Isaiah 49:14-16|
	            14. But Zion said, The LORD hath forsaken me, and my Lord hath forgotten me.\n
	 			15. Can a woman forget her sucking child, that she should not have compassion on the son of her womb? yea, they may forget, yet will I not forget thee.\n
	 			16. Behold, I have graven thee upon the palms of my hands; thy walls are continually before me. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Philippians 4:10-13|
            	10. But I rejoiced in the Lord greatly, that now at the last your care of me hath flourished again; wherein ye were also careful, but ye lacked opportunity.\n
				 11. Not that I speak in respect of want: for I have learned, in whatsoever state I am, therewith to be content.\n
				 12. I know both how to be abased, and I know how to abound: every where and in all things I am instructed both to be full and to be hungry, both to abound and to suffer need.\n
				 13. I can do all things through Christ which strengtheneth me.
            </item>
        <item>
            Hebrews 10:19-25|
            	19. Having therefore, brethren, boldness to enter into the holiest by the blood of Jesus,\n
				 20. By a new and living way, which he hath consecrated for us, through the veil, that is to say, his flesh;\n
				 21. And having an high priest over the house of God;\n
				 22. Let us draw near with a true heart in full assurance of faith, having our hearts sprinkled from an evil conscience, and our bodies washed with pure water.\n
				 23. Let us hold fast the profession of our faith without wavering; (for he is faithful that promised;)\n
				 24. And let us consider one another to provoke unto love and to good works:\n
				 25. Not forsaking the assembling of ourselves together, as the manner of some is; but exhorting one another: and so much the more, as ye see the day approaching. 
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="tired_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 34:15-22|
             	15. The eyes of the LORD are upon the righteous, and his ears are open unto their cry.\n
				 16. The face of the LORD is against them that do evil, to cut off the remembrance of them from the earth.\n
				 17. The righteous cry, and the LORD heareth, and delivereth them out of all their troubles.\n
				 18. The LORD is nigh unto them that are of a broken heart; and saveth such as be of a contrite spirit.\n
				 19. Many are the afflictions of the righteous: but the LORD delivereth him out of them all.\n
				 20. He keepeth all his bones: not one of them is broken.\n
				 21. Evil shall slay the wicked: and they that hate the righteous shall be desolate.\n
				 22. The LORD redeemeth the soul of his servants: and none of them that trust in him shall be desolate.
            </item>
        <item>
            Isaiah 40:25-31|
            	25. To whom then will ye liken me, or shall I be equal? saith the Holy One.\n
				 26. Lift up your eyes on high, and behold who hath created these things, that bringeth out their host by number: he calleth them all by names by the greatness of his might, for that he is strong in power; not one faileth.\n
				 27. Why sayest thou, O Jacob, and speakest, O Israel, My way is hid from the LORD, and my judgment is passed over from my God?\n
				 28. Hast thou not known? hast thou not heard, that the everlasting God, the LORD, the Creator of the ends of the earth, fainteth not, neither is weary? there is no searching of his understanding.\n
				 29. He giveth power to the faint; and to them that have no might he increaseth strength.\n
				 30. Even the youths shall faint and be weary, and the young men shall utterly fall:\n
				 31. But they that wait upon the LORD shall renew their strength; they shall mount up with wings as eagles; they shall run, and not be weary; and they shall walk, and not faint.
            </item>
        <item>
            Matthew 11:28-30|
	            28. Come unto me, all ye that labour and are heavy laden, and I will give you rest.\n
				29. Take my yoke upon you, and learn of me; for I am meek and lowly in heart: and ye shall find rest unto your souls.\n
				30. For my yoke is easy, and my burden is light.
            </item>
        <item>
            Hebrews 12:1-3|
             	1. Wherefore seeing we also are compassed about with so great a cloud of witnesses, let us lay aside every weight, and the sin which doth so easily beset us, and let us run with patience the race that is set before us,\n
				 2. Looking unto Jesus the author and finisher of our faith; who for the joy that was set before him endured the cross, despising the shame, and is set down at the right hand of the throne of God.\n
				 3. For consider him that endured such contradiction of sinners against himself, lest ye be wearied and faint in your minds. 
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="heaven_array">
        <item>
            John 3:16|
            	16. For God so loved the world, that he gave his only begotten Son, that whosoever believeth in him should not perish, but have everlasting life. 
            </item>
        <item>
            John 14:5-6|
            	5. Thomas saith unto him, Lord, we know not whither thou goest; and how can we know the way?\n
 				6. Jesus saith unto him, I am the way, the truth, and the life: no man cometh unto the Father, but by me.
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 6:20-23|
            	20. For when ye were the servants of sin, ye were free from righteousness.\n
				 21. What fruit had ye then in those things whereof ye are now ashamed? for the end of those things is death\n
				 22. But now being made free from sin, and become servants to God, ye have your fruit unto holiness, and the end everlasting life.\n
				 23. For the wages of sin is death; but the gift of God is eternal life through Jesus Christ our Lord.
            </item>
        <item>
            Romans 10:9-13|
             	9. That if thou shalt confess with thy mouth the Lord Jesus, and shalt believe in thine heart that God hath raised him from the dead, thou shalt be saved.\n
				 10. For with the heart man believeth unto righteousness; and with the mouth confession is made unto salvation.\n
				 11. For the scripture saith, Whosoever believeth on him shall not be ashamed.\n
				 12. For there is no difference between the Jew and the Greek: for the same Lord over all is rich unto all that call upon him.\n
				 13. For whosoever shall call upon the name of the Lord shall be saved.
            </item>
        <item>
            Epheasians 2:8-9|
             	8. For by grace are ye saved through faith; and that not of yourselves: it is the gift of God:\n
 				9. Not of works, lest any man should boast. 
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="pray_array">
        <item>
            Matthew 6:5-15|
	            5. And when thou prayest, thou shalt not be as the hypocrites are: for they love to pray standing in the synagogues and in the corners of the streets, that they may be seen of men. Verily I say unto you, They have their reward.\n
				6. But thou, when thou prayest, enter into thy closet, and when thou hast shut thy door, pray to thy Father which is in secret; and thy Father which seeth in secret shall reward thee openly.\n
				7. But when ye pray, use not vain repetitions, as the heathen do: for they think that they shall be heard for their much speaking.\n
				8. Be not ye therefore like unto them: for your Father knoweth what things ye have need of, before ye ask him.\n
				9. After this manner therefore pray ye: Our Father which art in heaven, Hallowed be thy name.\n
				10. Thy kingdom come, Thy will be done in earth, as it is in heaven.\n
				11. Give us this day our daily bread.\n
				12. And forgive us our debts, as we forgive our debtors.\n
				13. And lead us not into temptation, but deliver us from evil: For thine is the kingdom, and the power, and the glory, for ever. Amen.\n
				14. For if ye forgive men their trespasses, your heavenly Father will also forgive you:\n
				15. But if ye forgive not men their trespasses, neither will your Father forgive your trespasses.
            </item>
        <item>
            Matthew 7:7-11|
	            7. Ask, and it shall be given you; seek, and ye shall find; knock, and it shall be opened unto you:\n
				8. For every one that asketh receiveth; and he that seeketh findeth; and to him that knocketh it shall be opened.\n
				9. Or what man is there of you, whom if his son ask bread, will he give him a stone?\n
				10. Or if he ask a fish, will he give him a serpent?\n
				11. If ye then, being evil, know how to give good gifts unto your children, how much more shall your Father which is in heaven give good things to them that ask him?
            </item>
        <item>
            Mark 14:36|
            	36. And he said, Abba, Father, all things are possible unto thee; take away this cup from me: nevertheless not what I will, but what thou wilt. 
            </item>
        <item>
            John 15:7|
            	7. If ye abide in me, and my words abide in you, ye shall ask what ye will, and it shall be done unto you. 
            </item>
        <item>
            Philippians 4:6-7|
            	6. Be careful for nothing; but in every thing by prayer and supplication with thanksgiving let your requests be made known unto God.\n
 				7. And the peace of God, which passeth all understanding, shall keep your hearts and minds through Christ Jesus.
            </item>
        <item>
            I Thessalonians 5:17|
            	17. Pray without ceasing.
            </item>
        <item>
            I John 5:14-15|
            	14. And this is the confidence that we have in him, that, if we ask any thing according to his will, he heareth us:\n
 				15. And if we know that he hear us, whatsoever we ask, we know that we have the petitions that we desired of him.
            </item>
    </string-array>
    <string-array name="thankful_array">
        <item>
            Psalm 98|
            	1. O sing unto the LORD a new song; for he hath done marvellous things: his right hand, and his holy arm, hath gotten him the victory.\n
 				2. The LORD hath made known his salvation: his righteousness hath he openly shewed in the sight of the heathen.\n
				 3. He hath remembered his mercy and his truth toward the house of Israel: all the ends of the earth have seen the salvation of our God.\n
				 4. Make a joyful noise unto the LORD, all the earth: make a loud noise, and rejoice, and sing praise.\n
				 5. Sing unto the LORD with the harp; with the harp, and the voice of a psalm.\n
				 6. With trumpets and sound of cornet make a joyful noise before the LORD, the King.\n
				 7. Let the sea roar, and the fulness thereof; the world, and they that dwell therein.\n
				 8. Let the floods clap their hands: let the hills be joyful together\n
				 9. Before the LORD; for he cometh to judge the earth: with righteousness shall he judge the world, and the people with equity.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 100|
				1. Make a joyful noise unto the LORD, all ye lands.\n
				2. Serve the LORD with gladness: come before his presence with singing.\n
				3. Know ye that the LORD he is God: it is he that hath made us, and not we ourselves; we are his people, and the sheep of his pasture.\n
				4. Enter into his gates with thanksgiving, and into his courts with praise: be thankful unto him, and bless his name.\n
				5. For the LORD is good; his mercy is everlasting; and his truth endureth to all generations.
            </item>
        <item>
            Psalm 103|
				 1. Bless the LORD, O my soul: and all that is within me, bless his holy name.\n
				 2. Bless the LORD, O my soul, and forget not all his benefits:\n
				 3. Who forgiveth all thine iniquities; who healeth all thy diseases;\n
				 4. Who redeemeth thy life from destruction; who crowneth thee with lovingkindness and tender mercies;\n
				 5. Who satisfieth thy mouth with good things; so that thy youth is renewed like the eagle\'s.\n
				 6. The LORD executeth righteousness and judgment for all that are oppressed.\n
				 7. He made known his ways unto Moses, his acts unto the children of Israel.\n
				 8. The LORD is merciful and gracious, slow to anger, and plenteous in mercy.\n
				 9. He will not always chide: neither will he keep his anger for ever.\n
				 10. He hath not dealt with us after our sins; nor rewarded us according to our iniquities.\n
				 11. For as the heaven is high above the earth, so great is his mercy toward them that fear him.\n
				 12. As far as the east is from the west, so far hath he removed our transgressions from us.\n
				 13. Like as a father pitieth his children, so the LORD pitieth them that fear him.\n
				 14. For he knoweth our frame; he remembereth that we are dust.\n
				 15. As for man, his days are as grass: as a flower of the field, so he flourisheth.\n
				 16. For the wind passeth over it, and it is gone; and the place thereof shall know it no more.\n
				 17. But the mercy of the LORD is from everlasting to everlasting upon them that fear him, and his righteousness unto children\'s children;\n
				 18. To such as keep his covenant, and to those that remember his commandments to do them.\n
				 19. The LORD hath prepared his throne in the heavens; and his kingdom ruleth over all.\n
				 20. Bless the LORD, ye his angels, that excel in strength, that do his commandments, hearkening unto the voice of his word.\n
				 21. Bless ye the LORD, all ye his hosts; ye ministers of his, that do his pleasure.\n
				 22. Bless the LORD, all his works in all places of his dominion: bless the LORD, O my soul.
        </item>
        <item>
            I Thessalonians 5:16-18|
	            16. Rejoice evermore.\n
				17. Pray without ceasing.\n
				18. In every thing give thanks: for this is the will of God in Christ Jesus concerning you.
        </item>
    </string-array>
</resources>